Hi guys, good afternoon and welcome to this new jumpsuit up video. The last two jumpsuit up videos did really well.
Thanks for watching them. Leave a thumbs up and don't forget to subscribe to my channel.
Then you'll get notified if there's another video coming.
This is going to be the first video with two jumpsuits. These ones.
I ordered them at Fashion Nova because I thought they look really cool.
They did remind me a bit of some, I don't know, racing or grid girl outfits
I was not sure if I should order them in size small or extra small
I decided on extra small and now that I see this
I'm not sure if this was the right decision because it looks really narrow here
By the way, if you want to see more of this dress, check out my obscene videos
Because now I'm going to change into one of these
guitar solo
So I managed to squeeze into it.
I'm kind of surprised because it's rather stretchy.
I would definitely order one size up next time but yeah it's manageable.
Maybe if I wear it more often it gets even more stretchy.
So I'm not used to shoulder pads.
I think they give off some 80s vibes or something.
But now I'm really bossy with bright shoulders.
Now I need some shoes.
Now with the shoes it looks rather cool.
I kind of feel like I have to add some white accessories or something like that.
Thing is, I don't own white accessories because I do not own anything white.
Because I don't like white, to be honest.
But yeah, it's a nice look.
I feel this is kind of too bold here with the white.
I don't know.
I think the side lines are way cooler than the one in the front.
Yeah, overall, I feel that it's stretchy.
It's okay.
At least it sits really snug everywhere.
So yeah, I think this is not too bad.
I noticed that when I close it, the neck is really tight.
So I have to wear it more open.
If I should rate this one, if we go back to rating, I don't know, maybe a 7.
I wanted to take some pictures and I sat down and I noticed
this design works way better when I'm sitting. It's like it does make a better
silhouette. I don't know. I think this is really good sitting catsuit. If that's even a thing.
I just had a look at the product picture of this one and wow these are some hips.
I have no idea if that's going to fit me or if that's even possible. I'm really
curious about the no arm thing going on here and how this is going to look so let's see
Okay, I'm always amazed how two items with the same size can kind of differ so much because
this one is a lot wider than that one I don't know even the legs are even more
stretchy and wider and the waist here as well
yeah okay so one thing I noticed about some leggings and this catsuit as well
this seam here in Germany we will call it Rollwiese is really not stretchy and if
it's going right above the kneecap it's super hard to bend the knee because it does hurt
so i'm not sure about this one it's kind of loose in certain areas
and i'm really not a fan of the no arms cut out stuff here so this one was definitely the better
run. Yeah, kind of lost what I'm going to do with this one. At least the boots work nice together
with it. But yeah, overall I think this one is a five. It doesn't blow me away.
So since it really reminds me of some kind of bathing suit or a really sportive look,
some kind of scuba diving suit or whatever, I'm going to put a jacket on top of it.
And now I transferred it into a motorcycle biker suit, which I don't like that much as well.
So maybe let's just open the zipper. Better why, but I'm still not sure about the jacket.
I think I'm going to lose that again.
And again here's the thing with this seam here since it can't go straight over the kneecap
because it doesn't stretch it's going to I don't know go inwards which doesn't look good somehow.
Yeah not really satisfied with this cat suit. As I said this one is the winner.
This is really cool. I think I'll do some pictures with it or whatever. I hope you enjoyed this
episode of jumpsuit up. I'm sure we'll see each other in another video. Have a nice day. Bye.